Narrator: 7
Speaker: get angry
Narrator: 3
Speaker: get divorced
Narrator: 5
Speaker: get fit
Narrator: 4
Speaker: get lost
Narrator: 2
Speaker: get married
Narrator: 1
Speaker: get nervous
Narrator: 6
Speaker: get ready
Narrator: 9
Speaker: get better
get worse
Narrator: 8
Speaker: get colder
Narrator: 11
Speaker: get a job
Narrator: 12
Speaker: get a newspaper
Narrator: 10
Speaker: get a ticket
Narrator: 16
Speaker: get into a car
Narrator: 15
Speaker: get on a bus
Narrator: 13
Speaker: get on with somebody
Narrator: 14
Speaker: get up
Narrator: 18
Speaker: get home
Narrator: 19
Speaker: get to school
Narrator: 17
Speaker: get to work
Narrator: 21
Speaker: get an email
Narrator: 20
Speaker: get a present
Narrator: 22
Speaker: get a prize